My ten year catfish nightmare.
Sweet Bobby: My Catfish Nightmare is a documentary
film directed by Lyttanya Shannon.
Kirat falls for a man she meets online, only to get swept up in a virtual
relationship that upends her life for years, in this shocking documentary.
Self, played by Kirat Assi.
Self, played by Bobby Jandu.
Self, played by Sanj Jandu.
Kirat, played by Hemma Gulhane.
Bobby, played by Anurag Mehra.
Sanj, played by Ariya Larker.
Sweet Bobby: My Catfish Nightmare is a British true crime documentary film directed by
Lyttanya Shannon and released to streaming on Netflix on 16 October 2024.
The documentary is based on the 2021 Tortoise Media podcast of the same name, which tells the story of Kirat Assi, a woman who was
deceived by someone posing as a fictitious romantic partner named "Bobby Jandu" in an intricate catfishing scheme.